surehits.com 2015-05-20

# SureHits - For Insurance and Loans, It's SureHits!

  * Home
  * Advertisers
  * Publishers
  * Contact Us

## SureHits Privacy Policy

Internet consumer privacy is of paramount importance to SureHits and our advertisers. The following statement outlines our policies and principles regarding online privacy. SureHits is committed to protecting the privacy of consumers and to do our part to maintain the integrity and security of the Internet. Because of the changing nature of consumer needs and our business itself, SureHits reserves the right to modify this policy statement at any time without notice. As such, and since we want to always make certain that our privacy policy is clearly understood, we recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically to note any changes that may have occurred. Please forward any comments you may have regarding this policy to us at [ service@SureHits.com](mailto:service@SureHits.com).

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

When an Internet consumer clicks on one of Cyberspace Communication Corp.'s placed advertisements, Cyberspace Communication Corp. does not collect any personally identifiable information regarding the consumer who clicked on the ad (e.g. name, address, social security number, e-mail address).

In the course of providing the user a shopping experience, personally identifiable information may be provided to Cyberspace Communications Corp. This information will be temporarily stored for a reasonable length of time for the purposes of fulfilling the shopping experience. The personally identifiable information supplied by the user will not be permanently stored or archived. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)**

When an Internet consumer clicks on one of Cyberspace Communication Corp.'s placed advertisements, Cyberspace Communication Corp. collects what the industry terms as "ad delivery and reporting data" (Type of Browser, Operating System, IP address, domain type, page(s) visited, date and time of when an Internet consumer has responded to an advertisement). This type of information is defined by the Network Advertising Initiative (see Network Advertising Initiative section below) as Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII) "ad delivery and reporting data". This means that none of the data can be linked to any individual Internet consumer, and therefore it cannot be used for profiling purposes. 

Cyberspace Communication Corp. retains all ad delivery and reporting data indefinitely, for accounting and auditing purposes. 

In addition Cyberspace Communication Corp. does not collect any specific non-personally identifiable information (e.g. age, gender, interests, income-range) that could potentially be linked with other data to identify individual Internet consumers for the purpose of profiling. 

**Cookies**

When an Internet consumer views a Cyberspace Communication Corp. served advertisement for the first time, a cookie is placed within their computer. A cookie is a unique tag that is issued to the Internet customer and is used to identify individual computers. The purpose of the cookie is to allow the ad placement company to deliver advertisements that have a greater degree of relevance to the consumer, even though that consumer is, in essence, anonymous to the ad placement company. Consumers who wish to remove this cookie and disable their web browser from receiving further cookies can do so by following the instructions provided by their browser's manufacturer. 

**Ad management and Reporting Data - Use of Cookies**

When a consumer clicks on an ad placed by Cyberspace Communication Corp., they are assigned a unique number, known as a cookie, which is recorded and stored on their computer in their web browser's cookie file. Cookies do not harm Internet consumer's computers. 

Cookies help us to reach several of our key goals, such as providing Internet users with a more fulfilling, results oriented experience on the web, and increasing the amount of relevant material viewed by Internet consumers. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Client Data**

Cyberspace Communication Corp. sometimes collects non-personally identifiable information from our clients. Non-personally identifiable information is also known as "demographic" data and includes information such as age, gender, geographic location. We use this information to refer consumers to appropriate partners. 

**Personally Identifiable Client Data**

Cyberspace Communication Corp. collects personally identifiable information from all websites (and specifically their owners) wishing to use our service(s). The collection of this information is a part of normal business practices. Clients wishing to use our service(s) will be asked to provide personally identifiable data through the sign up and registration process at our web site. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. Cyberspace Communication Corp. will never request or collect data from a client on subject areas including sexual orientation, political or religious affiliations, or medical data. 

Cyberspace Communication Corp. does not use any personally identifiable data about a client for profiling purposes. All personally identifiable information that Cyberspace Communication Corp. collects from clients is principally intended for administrative needs (e.g., accounting), for which purpose such data are required. 

All personally identifiable data provided by individual clients will be kept in strict confidence by Cyberspace Communication Corp. and will be treated with the same level of respect and care that Cyberspace Communication Corp. treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets. Cyberspace Communication Corp. will never sell, rent, exchange or barter any personally identifiable information to or with any third party for financial gain or marketing purposes. 

**Security Precautions**

Cyberspace Communication Corp. makes every effort to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. Any data that is stored on Cyberspace Communication Corp.'s server is treated as proprietary and confidential. 

**Cyberspace Communications and Client Website Privacy Policy Statements**

Cyberspace Communication Corp. requests that website advertisers that are users of our services consent to and comply with the standards of online privacy. 

If you have particular concerns about any website advertising with Cyberspace Communication Corp. with respect to privacy issues, please contact [service@SureHits.com](mailto:service@SureHits.com). 

**Children's Privacy**

As of April 21, 2000 the children's Online Privacy Protection Act became effective. The regulations apply to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. Cyberspace Communication Corp. is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Cyberspace Communication Corp.'s web site, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. Our policy is not to permit anyone under the age of 13 to do business with us. If you believe your child has provided Cyberspace Communication Corp. with any personally identifiable data by registering at Cyberspace Communication Corp.'s web site, please contact [ service@SureHits.com](mailto:service@SureHits.com) to have them removed. 

**Contacting Us**

For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding Cyberspace Communication Corp.'s Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to [service@SureHits.com](mailto:service@SureHits.com), or you can send correspondence to the following address: 

Privacy - Cyberspace Communication Corp.  
1726 S. Kelly Ave.  
Edmond, OK 73013
